http://www.huschblackwell.com/privacy-policy#california-collection-notice

Introduction
Husch Blackwell LLP (“HB,” “we,” “our” or “us”) respects the privacy of your information. This privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us in using our websites, including our blogs and client portals (the “sites”), and the services provided through our sites (collectively referred to as the “services”).
From time to time, we may change this privacy policy. If we do, we will post an amended version on this webpage. Please review this privacy policy periodically. Your continued use of the sites and services after any such amendment signifies your acceptance thereof.
Collecting and using information
Personally identifiable information we collect online
Through your use of the sites and services, we may collect personally identifiable information from you. “Personally Identifiable Information” is individually identifiable information about an individual consumer that we collect online and that we maintain in an accessible form. We collect the following types of personally identifiable information:
Information you provide
We may collect the following personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us:
A first and last name
A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
An email address
A telephone number
Social Security Number
Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual
Information concerning a user that the sites or online service collects online from the user and maintains in personally identifiable form in combination with an identifier described above.
Interact with our sites or services. When you visit our sites; log in to an account you’ve created; send us any inquiries, feedback, questions, comments, suggestions or ideas; or interact with us in any way, you may need to provide us with your log-in information, name and/or email address.
Information as you navigate our sites
We automatically collect certain personally identifiable information through your use of the sites and services, such as the following:
Usage information: We collect information such as which pages on the sites you access, the frequency of access and what you click on while on the sites
Device information: We collect information about the device you are using, such as hardware model, operating system, application version number and browser
Mobile device information: In addition to the device information listed above, when you access our Sites via a browser on your mobile device, we collect and aggregate information about whether you are accessing the sites via a mobile device or tablet, device type, and carrier
Location information: We collect location information from site visitors on a city-regional basis
Third-party information
In some cases, we may receive certain personally identifiable information from you about a third party. For example, as part of our registration process, you may provide the name, email address and personal phone number of a third party. If you submit any personally identifiable information about another individual to us, you are responsible for making sure that you have the authority to do so and to allow us to use their personally identifiable information in accordance with this privacy policy.
How we use your personally identifiable information
We use the personally identifiable information we collect to provide the services to you, to improve our services and sites, and to protect our legal rights. In addition, we may use the personally identifiable information we collect to:
Process your account registration
Review your job application
Email you our blog posts
Contact you regarding our services or events that we feel may be of interest to you
Communicate with you about our Sites or Services or to inform you of any changes to our Sites or Services
Provide support
Maintain and improve our Sites and Services
Defend our legal rights and the rights of others
Efficiently maintain our business
Comply with applicable law
How we share your personally identifiable information
We may share the information that we collect about you in the following ways:
With service providers who perform data services on our behalf (e.g., email, hosting, maintenance, backup and analysis). Any such service providers will be under an obligation to us to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information
To service providers to prepare, deploy and analyze advertising content
To the extent that we are required to do so by law
In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings
To establish, exercise or defend our legal rights, including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention
To any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personally identifiable information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information
To any other person or entity as part of any business or asset sale
To any other person or entity where you consent to the disclosure
Cookies and other tracking technologies
We use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as pixels and web beacons) (collectively, “cookies”). Cookies are small files of information that are stored by your web browser software on your computer hard drive, mobile or other devices (e.g., smartphones or tablets).
We use Cookies to:
Estimate audience size and usage patterns
Understand and save your preferences for future visits, allowing us to customize the sites and services to your individual needs
Advertise new content, events and services that relate to your interests
Keep track of advertisements and search engine results
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions to resolve issues and offer better site experiences and tools in the future
Recognize when you return to the sites
We set some cookies ourselves and others are set by service providers. We use cookies set by service providers to provide us with useful information to help us improve our sites and services, to conduct advertising and to analyze the effectiveness of advertising.
Cookies can be blocked by changing your internet browser settings to refuse all or some cookies. If you choose to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the sites.
You can find out more about cookies and how to manage them by visiting www.AboutCookies.org.
You can understand which third parties have currently enabled cookies for your browser or mobile device and how to opt-out of some of those cookies by accessing the Network Advertising Initiative’s website or the Digital Advertising Alliance’s website. For more information on mobile specific opt-out choices, visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s Mobile Choices website.
Third-party processors
To ensure that your personally identifiable information receives an adequate level of protection, we have put in place appropriate procedures with the service providers we share your personally identifiable information with to ensure that your personally identifiable information is treated by those service providers in a way that is consistent with and which respects the applicable laws on data security and privacy. For example, we use cloud data storage, payroll processors, accounting software, payment processors and marketing service providers.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with the sites and services, compile reports on their activity, and provide other services related to their activity and usage. The technologies used by Google may collect information such as your internet protocol address, time of visit, whether you are a returning visitor and any referring website. The technologies used by Google Analytics do not gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policies. To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google, click here.
Google AdWords
We use Google AdWords for targeting and remarketing. We collect data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our sites, the website for which we serve advertisements, or the websites and online services where we display advertisements. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “remarketing”). We collect information about where you saw the ads we serve you and what ads you clicked on. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt-out Page.
Crazy egg
We use a third-party service, Crazy Egg, to analyze and improve the use of our pages. For more information about Crazy Egg, please visit their website. Crazy Egg may use cookies for one or more of the following purposes: user preference storage, A/B testing, usage pattern assessment, traffic analysis or advertisement performance assessment. Cookies placed by Crazy Egg do not include identifying information such as name, phone number, email address or mailing credentials. To opt out of Crazy Egg, follow the instructions to remove yourself from the data collection process.
Interest-based ads
We may use cookies and other technologies on our sites to collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites you visit in order to provide you with interest-based advertising. You can generally opt out of receiving interest-based advertisements from members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance by visiting their opt-out pages. When you opt out using these links, please note that you may still receive advertisements. They just will not be personalized based on your interests.
Surveys
We may ask you to voluntarily complete surveys. We will use any information that you voluntarily provide to us in those surveys to understand more about you. If you voluntarily chose to take a survey, you will be directed to a website hosted by Survey Monkey. Any personal information that you provide to Survey Monkey in response to a survey will be subject Survey Monkey’s privacy policy and terms of use. Survey Monkey will provide the survey results to us. The survey information is not anonymous.
“Do not track” signals
Some internet browsers incorporate a “do not track” feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Given that there is not a uniform way that browsers communicate the “do not track” signal, the sites do not currently interpret, respond to or alter its practices when it receives “do not track” signals.
Choices about your personally identifiable information
Review and request changes to your personally identifiable information
You may use your account to access, correct or view certain personally identifiable information we have collected and which is associated with your account. To review or request changes to any of your personally identifiable information, please contact us.
Marketing communications
To unsubscribe from emails from us, please click the unsubscribe link included in the footer of our emails. You also may submit a request to us.
Security
We maintain commercially reasonable security measures to protect the personally identifiable Information we collect and store from loss, misuse, destruction or unauthorized access. However, no security measure or modality of data transmission over the internet is 100 percent secure. Although we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee absolute security.
Third-party links
The sites may contain links that will let you leave the sites and services and access another website. Linked websites are not under our control. Except as stated below, this privacy policy applies solely to personally identifiable information that is acquired on these sites. We accept no responsibility or liability for these other websites.
Children's privacy
The sites are not intended for children under 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information from children under 16 years of age.
Data retention
We will store your information for as long as you are a client, our performance of the services require and as long as our ethical obligations require. We may keep records of transactions with you for a period of up to seven years to comply with the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) requirements.
Notice to Nevada residents
Nevada law allows Nevada residents to opt out of the sale of certain types of personal information. Subject to a number of exceptions, Nevada law defines “sale” to mean the exchange of certain types of personal information for monetary consideration to a person for the person to license or sell the information to additional persons. We do not currently sell personal information as defined in the Nevada law. However, if you are a Nevada resident, you still may submit a verified request to opt out of sales and we will record your instructions and incorporate them in the future if our policy changes. Opt-out requests may be sent to: privacy@huschblackwell.com.
Notice to California residents
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) requires that we provide California residents with a privacy policy that contains a comprehensive description of our online and offline practices regarding the collection, use, disclosure and sale of personal information and of the rights of California residents regarding their personal information.
The CCPA defines “personal information” to mean information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or household. Personal information does not include information that is publicly available, deidentified or aggregate. For purposes of this notice to California residents section, we will refer to this information as “personal information.”
Right to know about personal information collected, disclosed or sold
Your right
If you are a California resident, you have the right to request that we disclose what personal information we have collected about you in the 12-month period preceding your request. This right includes the right to request any or all of the following:
Specific pieces of personal information that we have collected about you
Categories of personal information we have collected about you
Categories of sources from which the personal information was collected
Categories of personal information that we sold (if applicable) or disclosed for a business purpose about you
Categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold (if applicable) or disclosed for a business purpose
The business or commercial purpose for collecting or, if applicable, selling personal information
The CCPA defines “sell” to mean selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a California resident’s personal information to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.
How to submit a request to know
You may submit a request to know by completing our online request form available here, emailing privacy@huschblackwell.com or by calling us at 1.800.711.5413.
Our process for verifying a request to know
We will comply with your request upon verification of your identity and, to the extent applicable, the identity of the California resident on whose behalf you are making such request. Our verification process may differ depending on whether you maintain a password-protected account with us.
If you maintain a password-protected account, we may verify your identity through existing authentication practices available through your account. Prior to disclosing the requested information, we will ask you to reauthenticate yourself with respect to that account.
If you do not maintain a password-protected account, or if you are an account holder but we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity with your account, we will verify your identity as follows:
Request to know categories of personal information: we will verify your identity to a reasonable degree of certainty by verifying at least two data points that you previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities.
Request to know specific pieces of personal information: we will verify your identity to a reasonably high degree of certainty by verifying at least three pieces of Personal Information previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities. In addition, you will be required to submit a signed declaration under penalty of perjury stating that you are the individual whose Personal Information is being requested.
Collection of personal information
The following table presents the categories of personal information that we have collected, the categories of sources from which that information was collected and the categories of third parties with whom we shared that Personal Information for the 12 months preceding the effective date of this privacy policy.
The CCPA defines “business purposes” to mean:
Auditing related to a current interaction with the consumer and concurrent transaction, including, but not limited to, counting ad impressions to unique visitors
Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, and prosecuting those responsible for that activity
Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality
Short-term, transient use, provided that the personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction
Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services
Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration
Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by us, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device
The CCPA defines “commercial purposes” to mean “to advance a person’s commercial or economic interests, such as by inducing another person to buy, rent, lease, join, subscribe to, provide, or exchange products, goods, property, information, or services, or enabling or effecting, directly or indirectly, a commercial transaction.”
For purposes of the below chart, we will refer to the business purposes by their above numbers and use the number (8) to reference the definition of commercial purposes.
Categories of personal information collected
Categories of sources from which personal information was collected
Business or commercial purpose for the collection
Categories of third parties with whom we share personal information
Name
Clients/case information
Prospective clients
Site users
Government entities
(2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Law enforcement/legal requests
Email address
Clients/case information
Prospective clients
Site users
Third-party companies
(2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Law enforcement/legal requests
Postal address
Clients / case information
Prospective clients
Third-party companies
(2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Law enforcement/legal requests
Telephone number
Clients/case information
Prospective clients
Site users
(2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Law enforcement/legal requests
Driver’s license number, other type of state identification card number, passport number
Clients/case information
(2) & (5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Social Security Number
Clients
(2) & (5)
Signature
Clients/case information
(2) & (5)
Service providers
Law enforcement/legal requests
Credit and debit card number; other financial information (e.g., financial account number)
Clients
(2), (5) & (8)
Service providers
Insurance policy number or subscriber identification number
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Professional or employment-related information
Clients/case information
Site users
(5) & (8)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Telephone numbers or other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers that can be used to identify a particular consumer or device
Clients/case information
Site users
(1) & (8)
Data analytics providers
Other online identifier
Clients
Site users
(1), (7) & (8)
Data analytics providers
Browsing history and search history
Site users
Third-party companies
(5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Data analytics providers
Advertising networks
Geolocation data
Site users
Third-party companies
(5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Data analytics providers
Advertising networks
Internet protocol address
Site users
Third-party companies
(1), (2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Data analytics provider
Advertising networks
Physical characteristics or description
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Customer number, unique pseudonym or user alias (e.g., user name)
Clients/case information
Third-party companies
(2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Data analytics providers
Cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers or other similar technology
Site users
Third-party companies
(2), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Data analytics providers
Advertising networks
Information regarding consumer’s interaction with website, application or advertisement
Site users
Third-party companies
(1), (2), (3), (5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Data analytics providers
Advertising networks
Records of personal property
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Records of products or services purchased, obtained or considered
Clients/case information
(5), (6), (7) & (8)
Service providers
Medical information
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Education information
Clients/case information
(5), (6), (7) & (8)
Law enforcement / legal requests
Race, color. national origin, ancestry
Clients / case information
(5), (6) & (7)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Religion (includes religious dress and grooming practices)
Clients/case information
(5), (6) & (7)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Disability
Clients/case information
(5), (6) & (7)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Citizenship status
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Military or veteran status
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Marital status
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Sex/gender, gender identity/expression, sexual orientation
Clients/case information
(5), (6) & (7)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Age
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Political affiliations or activities
Clients/case information
Third-party companies
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Requests for leave (own serious health condition, pregnancy, family care)
Clients/case information
(5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Imagery of the face (photographs)
Clients/case information
(2) & (5)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Audio/voice recordings
Clients/case information
(5)
Not applicable
Inferences drawn from above information to create a profile about consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes
Clients/case information
Third-party  companies
(5), (6), (7) & (8)
Law enforcement/legal requests
Disclosure or sale of personal information
The following is a list of categories of personal information that we have sold to third parties in the 12 months preceding the effective date of this privacy policy solely for the purpose of retargeting advertising:
Cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers or other similar technology
Internet protocol address
Information regarding consumer’s interaction with website, application or advertisement
The following is a list of categories of personal information that we have disclosed for a business purpose in the 12 months preceding the effective date of this privacy policy:
Name
Email address
Postal address
Telephone number
Driver’s license number; other type of state identification card number; passport number*
Signature*
Credit and debit card number, other financial information (e.g., financial account number)
Insurance policy number or subscriber identification number*
Professional or employment-related information*
Telephone numbers or other forms of persistent or probabilistic identifiers that can be used to identify a particular consumer or device*
Other online identifier
Browsing history and search history
Geolocation data*
Internet protocol address
Physical characteristics or description*
Customer number, unique pseudonym or user alias (e.g., user name)*
Cookies, beacons, pixel tags, mobile ad identifiers or other similar technology
Information regarding consumer’s interaction with website, application or advertisement
Records of personal property*
Records of products or services purchased, obtained or considered*
Medical information*
Education information*
Race, color, national origin, ancestry*
Religion (includes religious dress and grooming practices)*
Disability*
Citizenship status*
Military or veteran status*
Marital status*
Sex/gender, gender identity/expression, sexual orientation*
Age*
Political affiliations or activities*
Requests for leave (own serious health condition, pregnancy, family care)*
Imagery of the face (photographs)
Inferences drawn from above information to create a profile about consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities and aptitudes*
*Denotes personal information which we collect, use, and disclose through the nature of our legal representation and provision of legal services for clients. Disclosure of this information will be limited to required or strategic disclosures related to our legal representation. We do not otherwise collect, use or disclose this information.
Right to request deletion of personal information
Your right
If you are a California resident, you have the right to request that we delete the personal information about you that we have collected or maintain. However, a business is not required to comply with a request to delete if it is necessary for the business to maintain the personal information in order to, for example, complete a transaction, detect security incidents, comply with a legal obligation or otherwise use the Personal Information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which the consumer provided the information.
How to submit a request to delete
You may submit a request to delete by completing our online request form available here, emailing privacy@huschblackwell.com or by calling us at 1-800-711-5413.
If you submit a request to delete online, you will be asked to confirm separately that you want your personal information deleted.
Our process for verifying a request
We will comply with your request upon verification of your identity and, to the extent applicable, the identity of the California resident on whose behalf you are making such request. Our verification process may differ depending on whether you maintain a password-protected account with us.
If you maintain a password-protected account, we may verify your identity through existing authentication practices available through your account. Prior to deleting the personal information, we will ask you to reauthenticate yourself with respect to that account.
If you do not maintain a password-protected account, or if you are an account holder but we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity with your account, we will verify your identity either to a reasonable degree of certainty or a reasonably high degree of certainty depending on the sensitivity of the personal information and the risk of harm to you by unauthorized deletion.
We will verify your identity to a reasonable degree of certainty by verifying at least two data points that you previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities.
We will verify your identity to a reasonably high degree of certainty by verifying at least three pieces of Personal Information previously provided to us and which we have determined to be reliable for the purpose of verifying identities. In addition, you will be required to submit a signed declaration under penalty of perjury stating that you are the individual whose personal information is being requested.
If we are unable to verify your identity to the applicable standard, we will treat your request to delete as a request to opt out of the sale of the personal information that you provided as part of processing the request to delete. See the following section for a description of the right to opt out of the sale of personal information.
Notice of right to opt-out of sale of personal information
Your right
If you are a California resident, you have the right to direct a business that sells (or may in the future sell) your personal information to stop selling your personal information and to refrain from doing so in the future.
The CCPA defines “sell” to mean selling, renting, releasing, disclosing, disseminating, making available, transferring or otherwise communicating orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means, a California resident’s personal information to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration.
How to submit a request to opt out
You may submit a request to opt-out of sales through our interactive webform available by clicking on this link: “Do Not Sell My Personal Information.” You also may submit a request by emailing privacy@huschblackwell.com or calling 1.800.711.5413.
How we process a request to opt out
We will act upon your request to opt-out within 15 days from the date that you submit the request. The CCPA does not require that we verify the identity of individuals who submit requests to opt out of sales. However, we may deny the request if we have a good-faith, reasonable and documented belief that the request is fraudulent. If we deny the request on this basis, we will notify the requesting party and provide an explanation why we believe the request is fraudulent.
Right to nondiscrimination for the exercise of a California resident’s privacy rights
We will not discriminate against California residents if they exercise any of the rights provided in the CCPA as described in this section notice to California Residents. As such, we will not deny goods or services to that California resident; charge different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties; provide a different level or quality of goods or services to the California resident; or suggest that the California resident will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services. However, we are permitted to charge a California resident a different price or rate, or provide a different level or quality of goods or services, if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to us by the individual’s data.
Authorized agents
California residents may use an authorized agent to submit a request to know, delete or opt out of sales on your behalf.
If you use an authorized agent to submit a request to know or request to delete, we may require that: (1) the authorized agent provide proof of your written permission; and (2) you verify your identity directly with us. These requirements do not apply if you have provided the authorized agent with a power of attorney pursuant to California Probate Code sections 4000 to 4465.
If you use an authorized agent to submit a request to opt out of sales, you will need to provide that authorized agent with written permission to do so and submit written proof to us that the agent has been authorized to act on your behalf.
Shine the light law
We do not disclose personal information obtained through our site or services to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Accordingly, we have no obligations under California Civil Code § 1798.83.
Accessibility
We are committed to ensuring this privacy policy is accessible to individuals with disabilities. If you wish to access this privacy policy in an alternative format, please contact us as described below.
Notice to residents of European economic area and the United Kingdom
Husch Blackwell LLP (“HB,” “we” or “us”) is a general practice law firm that provides legal services in a number of specialties within varying industries. HB is committed to protecting your privacy and utilizing technology that gives you a powerful and safe online experience. The website www.huschblackwell.com is owned and operated by HB and HB is the controller of the personal data.
We collect and share information from the users of our sites and during the performance of our services to manage our contractual obligations to you, comply with legal obligations and/or because we have a legitimate business interest to do so. We collect and share information to: (a) provide our sites and services, and legal services; (b) provide information about our products and services; (c) provide information about data security and privacy; (d) learn more about our customer’s preferences; (e) enhance, personalize and support your experience on our sites; (f) enhance and develop our products and services based on your direct comments and/or on the pages or information you view on our sites; and (g) analyze the traffic to our sites.
Under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you have the following rights related to HB’s use of your personal data:
Number
Description of your right
Right 1
A right to access personal data held by us about you, as well as information about how we are using your data.
Right 2
A right to require us to rectify any inaccurate personal data held by us about you.
Right 3
A right to require us to erase personal data held by us about you, and where the personal data has been made public, for other controllers processing the personal data to also erase links to, or copy or replication of, such personal data.  This right will only apply where (for example): we no longer need to use the personal data to achieve the purpose we collected it for; or where you withdraw your consent if we are using your personal data based on your consent; or where you object to the way we process your data (in line with Right 6 below).
Right 4
A right to restrict our processing of personal data held by us about you.  This right will only apply where (for example): you dispute the accuracy of the personal data held by us; or where you would have the right to require us to erase the personal data but would prefer that our processing is restricted instead; or where we no longer need to use the personal data to achieve the purpose we collected it for, but you require the data for the purposes of dealing with legal claims.
Right 5
A right to receive personal data, which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format.  You also have the right to require us to transfer this personal data to another organization, at your request.
Right 6
A right to object to our processing of personal data held by us about you (including for the purposes of sending marketing materials to you).
Right 7
A right to withdraw your consent, where we are relying on it to use your personal data (for example, to provide you with marketing information about our services or products).
If you have consented to receive communications from us, you can contact us at any time to have your details removed from lists used by us or to update your marketing preferences. Please email privacy@huschblackwell.com and quote your email/telephone number/account number in the body of the email, telling us what you would like us to do.
You can also click “unsubscribe” on any of our emails, and we will ensure we don't send you any communications of this nature in future.
To exercise any of your rights above, please contact HB at privacy@huschblackwell.com. If you choose to exercise any of your rights listed above, it may affect your ability to use the sites, as the operation and functionalities provided on the sites may require the use of your personally identifiable information.
How to contact us
To contact us for questions or concerns about our privacy policies or practices, please email privacy@huschblackwell.com or call 1.800.711.5413.
The choice of a lawyer is an important decision and should not be based solely upon advertisements.
Past results afford no guarantee of future results. Every case is different and must be judged on its own merits.
The choice of a lawyer is an important decision and should not be based solely upon advertisements.
Past results afford no guarantee of future results. Every case is different and must be judged on its own merits.
Close Subscribe Prompt
Stay updated.
Subscribe to receive Husch Blackwell’s news and insights.
Select your preferences
